<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SwitchingFragmentApp</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="content_one">I decided to revise my argumentative synthesis essay first because this essay just required a lot of attention as I was mostly excited about fixing this essay completely. I started out by deleting and rewriting both of my main body paragraphs. The reason for this was because unlike my first and third essay I had not put any effort into the essay itself as i had a really difficult time writing this particular essay. In more detail it was my first time using sources to the fullest which ended up being more of a challenge than i thought it would. Overall i ended up failing as a writer and ended up rewriting what the sources had to say and i failed in putting it into my own words thus plagiarizing became the heart of the problem so deleting the paragraphs and rewriting them was crucial for this revision. The topic i had chosen for my essay was how coffee has been more beneficial towards our modern world scientifically and economically than beer and wine I started out by rewriting my entire first body paragraph which had a lot to do with coffee and its crucial role to the United States, and the South American economy. I had to delete the majority of this paragraph and re-read all my sources. I rewrote this paragraph and stated out in a lot of detail the importance and beneficial role that coffee had to play in the American economy. This time I did so in my own words. I elaborated in all the details such as how coffee affected small coffee houses and how it contributed in the making of worldwide jobs. The organization in this essay wasn \'t so great so i ended up organizing it much better. I started out by first talking about how coffee benefited the U.S economy, and then i moved on into the effects it had on the South American economy.</string>
    <string name="content_two">- Texas v. Johnson Argumentative To this day, Americans have many rights and privileges. Rights stated in the United States constitution may be simple and to the point, but the rights Americans have may cause debate to whether or not something that happens in society, is completely reasonable. The Texas v. Johnson case created much debate due to a burning of the American Flag. One may say the burning of the flag was tolerable because of the rights citizens of the United States have, another may say it was not acceptable due to what the American flag symbolizes for America - Argumentative Essay: Animal Testing The world is full of chemicals and companies trying to make the most “bang” for their buck. What most people don \'t know is that behind most large manufacturing companies sits poor tortured animals rotting away in cages being used for the experimental needs of humans. In the United States alone 100 million animals are used on yearly bases. (Shell Ethics) Animal testing is NOT needed for any reason-it’s killing animals, it’s cruel, and alternative methods are available....
    - Texas v. Johnson Argumentative To this day, Americans have many rights and privileges. Rights stated in the United States constitution may be simple and to the point, but the rights Americans have may cause debate to whether or not something that happens in society, is completely reasonable. The Texas v. Johnson case created much debate due to a burning of the American Flag. One may say the burning of the flag was tolerable because of the rights citizens of the United States have, another may say it was not acceptable due to what the American flag symbolizes for America - Argumentative Essay: Animal Testing The world is full of chemicals and companies trying to make the most “bang” for their buck. What most people don \'t know is that behind most large manufacturing companies sits poor tortured animals rotting away in cages being used for the experimental needs of humans. In the United States alone 100 million animals are used on yearly bases. (Shell Ethics) Animal testing is NOT needed for any reason-it’s killing animals, it’s cruel, and alternative methods are available....
        - Texas v. Johnson Argumentative To this day, Americans have many rights and privileges. Rights stated in the United States constitution may be simple and to the point, but the rights Americans have may cause debate to whether or not something that happens in society, is completely reasonable. The Texas v. Johnson case created much debate due to a burning of the American Flag. One may say the burning of the flag was tolerable because of the rights citizens of the United States have, another may say it was not acceptable due to what the American flag symbolizes for America - Argumentative Essay: Animal Testing The world is full of chemicals and companies trying to make the most “bang” for their buck. What most people don \'t know is that behind most large manufacturing companies sits poor tortured animals rotting away in cages being used for the experimental needs of humans. In the United States alone 100 million animals are used on yearly bases. (Shell Ethics) Animal testing is NOT needed for any reason-it’s killing animals, it’s cruel, and alternative methods are available....
    </string>
</resources>
